Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
- VIII. Executive officers' papers, 1914-1971. (Box 112-155)
  - D. Joseph Schlossberg correspondence, 1930-1940. (Box 135-145)
    - 3. General correspondence.
      - Clothing Contractors Association (1938) (Box 137, Folder 35)
      - Clothing Workers Federation (France) 1937 (Box 137, Folder 36)
      - Cohen, Alex (1935) Manager, Shirt Makers Joint Board (Box 137, Folder 37)
      - Cohen, William (American Committee for the Settlement of Jews in Birobidjan) 1936 (Box 137, Folder 38)
      - Coit, Eleanor (Affiliated Schools for Workers) 1936 (Box 137, Folder 39)
      - Columbus, Ohio Federation of Labor (1936) (Box 137, Folder 40)
      - Committee on Academic Freedom - American Civil Liberties Union (re threatened 1936 state investigation (Box 137, Folder 41)
      - Committee to Celebrate the President's birthday (Franklin Roosevelt) 1938 (Box 137, Folder 42)
      - Committee for Defense of Civil Rights in Tampa (1936) (Box 137, Folder 43)
      - Committee for German Refugees (1936-38) (Box 137, Folder 44)
      - Common Sense (Selden Rodman) 1937 (Box 137, Folder 45)
      - Community Church of New York (1938) (Box 137, Folder 46)
      - Community Council of the City of N.Y. (1936) (Box 137, Folder 47)
      - C.I.O. (1936-40) correspondence with Director John Brophy, Comptroller J.R. Bell (Box 137, Folder 48)
      - Connecticut Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 137, Folder 49)
      - Construction Workers Organizing Committee (1939) (Box 137, Folder 50)
      - Coordinator of Industrial Cooperation (E. J. Tracy, U.S. Dept. of Labor) 1936 (Box 137, Folder 51)
      - Copeland, Royal (Senator, Fla.) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Curlee Clothing Workers (St. Louis) Strike Committee (1938) (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Custom & Uniform Tailors (1938) (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - C (general) (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Danish, Max (Justice) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - The Day (S. Margoshes, Editor) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Deborah Jewish Tuberculosis Society (1935-38) (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Debs, Theodore (1935) (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Debs Labor School (1938-39) (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Deiches, Maurice (attorney, New York State) re assembly bill dealing with ladies' garments. (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Del Norte Industrial Union CouncilDining Car Employees Union (N.Y.) 1939 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Doll and Toy Workers Union (1935) (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - Dress and Waist Pressers Union (ILGWU) 1936-39 (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - Dubinsky, David (ILGWU) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - D (general) (Box 138, Folder 18)
      - Electrical Workers Union (United) District #4 Brooklyn (strike committee) 1938 (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - Emergency Peace Campaign (Kirby Page) 1935 (Box 138, Folder 20)
      - Enameling & Stamping Mill Employees (1935) (Box 138, Folder 21)
      - E (general) (Box 138, Folder 22)
      - Fairchild, Henry Pratt (Commonwealth Federation of N.Y.) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 23)
      - Farmer Labour Party Committee (1936) (Box 138, Folder 24)
      - Federal Council of Churches in America (1939) (Box 138, Folder 25)
      - Federated Trade Council (Reading, Pa.) 1937 (Box 138, Folder 26)
      - Federation of Flint Glass Workers (1935) (Box 138, Folder 27)
      - Federation of Jews in America (1936) (Box 138, Folder 28)
      - Ferrero-Sallitto Defense Committee (1937) (Box 138, Folder 29)
      - Fine, Nathan (American Commonwealth Political Federation) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 30)
      - Flanagan's (Father's) Boys Home (1939) (Box 138, Folder 31)
      - Flynn, John (re appointment of Board of Higher Education) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 32)
      - Food Organizer (AFL-Food Workers Union) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 33)
      - Free Synagogue of N.Y. (1937) (Box 138, Folder 34)
      - Foreign Language Information Service (1936) (Box 138, Folder 35)
      - Freie Arbeiter Stimme (1939) (Box 138, Folder 36)
      - Friedenwald, Harry (1938) (Box 138, Folder 37)
      - Friends of Spanish Democracy (1936) (Box 138, Folder 38)
      - Fur Workers Union (International) 1937 (Box 138, Folder 39)
      - F (general) (Box 138, Folder 40)
      - Galacian Jews of America (United) 1937 (Box 138, Folder 41)
      - Gerber, Julius (Socialist Party Campaign Committee) 1938 (Box 138, Folder 42)
      - Giovanitti, Arturo (Italian Labor Education Bureau) 1938 (Box 138, Folder 43)
      - Glove Workers Union (International) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 44)
      - Goldberg, E. (ACWA Milwaukee Plant, 1929 financial statement) 1930 (Box 138, Folder 45)
      - Goldberg, Louis (attorney, Shiplacoff Park Committee) 1938 (Box 138, Folder 46)
      - Golden, Clinton (Pittsburgh Regional Director, NLRB) 1936 (Box 138, Folder 47)
      - Green, William (President, AFL) 1935-36 (Box 138, Folder 48)
      - Guild for German Cultural Freedom (1939) (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - G (general) (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Hamlin, I. (Nat'l. Labor Comm.) 1936 (Box 139, Folder 2a)
      - Har Sinai Congregation (1937) (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Harlem Labor Committee (1935) (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Harris, Abram L. (Sociologist) Potofsky to (1937) (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (Dept. of Labor) (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers Union (1936) (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Hebrew Butcher Workers Union (Joseph Blesky) 1935 (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Hebrew Sheltering and Immigrant Aid Society (1935-39) (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Hebrew Teachers Union (1938) (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Hebrew Trade (United) Morris Feinstone (1938) (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Hebrew University (American Friends of) 1937 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Heeg, Ivan der (International Federation of Clothing Workers re ACWA affiliation) 1936-39 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Heinrich, Dorothea (Brookwood Labor College) 1936 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Held, Adolph (ACWA attorney) 1937 (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Hendley, Charles (Teachers Union of the City of N.Y.) 1936 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - Highlander Folk School (Monteagle, Tenn.) 1935 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Hillman, Sidney (Schlossberg to) 1937 (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Hillyer, Mary (League of Industrial Democracy) 1935-36 (Box 139, Folder 19)
      - Hochstein, Joshua (Anti-Semitism in Mexico) 1938 (Box 139, Folder 20)
      - Hollander, Louis (co-manager, N.Y. Joint Board) 1936 (Box 139, Folder 21)
      - Holmes, John Haynes (Community Church) 1938 (Box 139, Folder 22)
      - Hook, Sidney (John Dewey Labor Research Fund) 1939 (Box 139, Folder 23)
      - Hosiery Workers (American Federation of) 1935 (Box 139, Folder 24)
      - Hotel (reservations and confirmations) 1935-40 (Box 139, Folder 25)
      - House of Journals (Jerusalem) 1939 (Box 139, Folder 26)
      - Howe, Benjamin (NYC Fusion Party) 1938 (Box 139, Folder 27)
      - Hudson Shore Labor School (1939) (Box 139, Folder 28)
      - Hull, Cordell (Secretary of State) 1938 (Box 139, Folder 29)
      - Hunter College (Schlossberg's correspondence as member of the Board of Higher Education) 1936-39 (Box 139, Folder 30)
      - H (general) 1935-39 (Box 139, Folder 31)
      - Ice Cream Workers Union (Local 239, Brooklyn) 1935 (Box 139, Folder 32)
      - Illinois Labor Dept. (1936) (Box 139, Folder 33)
      - Illinois Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 139, Folder 34)
      - Illinois Labor Party (1936) (Box 139, Folder 35)
      - Immigration and Naturalization (US Dept. of) 1939 (Box 139, Folder 36)
      - Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of North America (Camden, N.J. Strike, 1935) (Box 139, Folder 37)
      - Insurance Companies (ACWA policies) 1935-38 (Box 139, Folder 38)
      - International Ladies Handbag, Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union (1937) (Box 139, Folder 39)
      - International Workingmen's Association (appeal for funds) 1936 (Box 139, Folder 40)
      - Iowa State Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 139, Folder 41)
      - Isaacs, Stanley (Manhattan Borough President) 1939 (Box 139, Folder 42)
      - Israel Zion Hospital (1936) (Box 139, Folder 43)
      - Ives, Irving (NY assemblyman) telegraph, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 44)
      - I (general) (Box 139, Folder 45)
      - Jewish Club, Inc. (re symposium the future of labor and industry) 1937 (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Jewish Conciliation Board of America (1939) (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Jewish Consumptive Relief Society (1935-40) (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - Jewish Daily Forward (B.C. Vladeck and Abraham Cahan) 1935-39 (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - Jewish Educational Association (1938) (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Jewish Frontier (correspondence re civil war in the labor movement) 1936-37 (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Jewish Journal and Daily News (1939) (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Jewish Labor Committee (1935) (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Jewish National Workers Alliance of America (1935-37) (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Jewish Socialist Verband of America (1936-37) (Box 140, Folder 9a)
      - Joint Boycott Council (American Jewish Congress) 1938 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - Journeymen Tailors Union (1935-40) (Box 140, Folder 10a)
      - J (general) (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - Kansas Emergency Relief Committee (1935) (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - Kaufman, Belle (1936) (Box 140, Folder 13)
      - Keep America Out of War Congress (correspondence with Alice Dodge and Clarence Senior) 1938-39 (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - Kentucky Miners Defense (fund raising for Harlan County miners) 1935-36 (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - Knit Goods Workers Union (Joint Council - ILGWU) 1936 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - Kokomo (Ind.) Trades and Labor Council (1936) (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - Krzycki, Leo (2 telegrams re rubber workers strike) 1936 (Box 140, Folder 18)
      - Kuhlman, Griselda (organizer, Norfolk, Va.) 1935 (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - K (general) (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - La Follette, Robert (Senator, Wisconsin) 1936 (Box 140, Folder 21)
      - La Guardia, Fiorello (Mayor of N.Y.) 1936-38 (Box 140, Folder 21a)
      - Labor Committee of the Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (1935) (Box 140, Folder 22)
      - Labor Committee for Jewish Palestine (1938-39) (Box 140, Folder 23)
      - Labor Defense (International) 1937 (Box 140, Folder 24)
      - Labor Department (U.S.) 1936-40 (Box 140, Folder 25)
      - Labor Organization Committee (International) 1938 (Box 140, Folder 26)
      - Labor's Non-Partisan League (E.L. Oliver) 1938 (Box 140, Folder 27)
      - Labor Review (1937) (Box 140, Folder 28)
      - Labor Stage (correspondence with Louis Schaffner and Rose Schneiderman) 1936 (Box 140, Folder 29)
      - Labor Temple (Detroit and St. Paul, MN) 1936-37 (Box 140, Folder 30)
      - Laborer's Union of America (1937) (Box 140, Folder 31)
      - Ladies Garment Workers (International Union) includes correspondence with David Dubinsky (1935-37) (Box 140, Folder 32)
      - Laidler, Harry (League for Industrial Democracy) 1937 (Box 140, Folder 33)
      - Land, Rosser Rev. Leon (1936) (Box 140, Folder 34)
      - Lanzetta, James (Congressman, N.Y.) 1937 (Box 140, Folder 35)
      - Lauck, William (CIO Economist) 1938 (Box 140, Folder 36)
      - Lawson, John (Quarry Workers International Union) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - League for Industrial Democracy (including correspondence with Harry Laidler and Mary Hillyer) (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - League for Labor Palestine (1936-38) (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Legal Aid Society (re lay off of NY clothing worker) 1938 (Box 141, Folder 4)
      - Lee, Algernon (1935) congratulations on appointment of Board of Higher Education (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Lehman, Herbert (Governor of N.Y.) 1938 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Levin, Lawrence (Local 177, Fall River, Mass. registration card for convention) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Levin, Samuel (Chicago Joint Board) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Levin, William (Investment Counsel) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 9)
      - Levitas, S.M. (New Leader) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Levitt, J. (Jewish Daily Forward) 1935 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - Levy, Matthew (Judge NY Municipal Court) 1938 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Lewis, John L. (United Mine Workers of America) 1936-1939 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Libby, Frederick J. (National Council for the Prevention of War) 1939 (Box 141, Folder 14)
      - Lieberman, Elias (N.Y.attorney) 1938 (Box 141, Folder 14a)
      - Lochner, Louis (Associated Press) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - Lore, Ludwig (1936) (Box 141, Folder 16)
      - Los Angeles Sanitarium (1939) (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - Lowenthal, Max (ACWA attorney, 1926-38) (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - L (general) (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - McConnell, Bishop Francis (1939) (Box 141, Folder 20)
      - McGoldrick, Joseph (City Club of N.Y.) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 21)
      - Machinists (International Association of) Transport Workers Lodge, 1936 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      - Mack, Walter (1936) (Box 141, Folder 23)
      - Madison (Wisconsin) Federation of Labor (re union label) 1935 (Box 141, Folder 24)
      - Maine Federation of Labor (1936) (Box 141, Folder 25)
      - Maisel, Max (bookseller) 1939 (Box 141, Folder 26)
      - Maison Syndicale (Belgium) re Schlossberg's Workers and their World (1936) (Box 141, Folder 27)
      - Manhattan Merchant Tailors Association (1938) (Box 141, Folder 28)
      - Marcantonio, Vito (Congressman,N.Y.) 1935 (Box 141, Folder 29)
      - Marconi, Delores (Washable Jackets, Knee Pants and Novelty Workers Union) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 30)
      - Marimpietri, A.D. (Amalgamated Trust and Savings Bank, Chicago) 1936 (Box 141, Folder 31)
      - Massachusetts State Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 141, Folder 32)
      - Medem Sanitorium in Poland (1938) (Box 141, Folder 33)
      - Medical Bureau to Aid Spanish Democracy (1937) (Box 141, Folder 34)
      - Menomenee (Michigan) 1937 (Box 141, Folder 35)
      - Merchandise Service and Delivery Workers Union (1937) (Box 141, Folder 36)
      - Merritt, Matthew (Congressman, N.Y.S.) (Box 141, Folder 37)
      - Meissig, Felix (1936) (Box 141, Folder 38)
      - Methodist Federation for Social Service (1935) (Box 141, Folder 39)
      - Meyer, Max (Arbitrator) 1939 (Box 141, Folder 40)
      - Meyerson, Goldie (Schlossberg to) 1938 (Box 141, Folder 41)
      - Michigan Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 141, Folder 41a)
      - Mikol, David (1939) (Box 141, Folder 42)
      - Milk Consumers Protective Committee (1935) (Box 141, Folder 43)
      - Milwaukee Dept. of Outdoor Relief (1935-36) (Box 141, Folder 44)
      - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Union (1937) (Box 141, Folder 45)
      - Mine Workers of America (United) correspondence with secretary-treasurer Thomas Kennedy re cooperative work in West Virginia, Kentucky and Pennsylvania (1935-40) (Box 141, Folder 46)
      - Minnesota Progressive Volunteers Committee (1936) (Box 141, Folder 47)
      - Mississippi Federation of Labor (1936) (Box 141, Folder 48)
      - Monat, Peter (N.Y. Joint Board) telegram, 1937 (Box 141, Folder 49)
      - Mooney, Thomas (Defense Committee) 1936-37 (Box 141, Folder 50)
      - Morgenthau, Henry (1939) (Box 141, Folder 51)
      - Morrison, Frank (secretary, AFL) correspondence re per capita tax (1935-37) (Box 141, Folder 52-53)
      - Moskowitz, Henry (1935-36) (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Most, Amicus (Gelluloid, Catalin and Galilth Workers Union (1935) (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Mumford, Lewis (1935-38) (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Murray, Richard (Galena Defense Committee) 1937 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Musicians (American Federation of) 1939 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - M (general) (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - National Association of Union Manufacturers (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - National Conference of Christians and Jews (1938) (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - National Council for Jewish Women (1935) (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - National Council for Social Democracy (1939) (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - National Council for the Prevention of War (1936) (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - National Council of Labour (London) Help for the Workers of Spain (1935) (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - National Federation of Post Office Clerks (1935) (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - National Industrial Conference Board (1935) (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - National Industrial Reconstructive Alliance (1936) (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - National Jewish Fund (1938) (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - National Labor Committee for Palestine (1937) (Box 142, Folder 17)
      - National Labor Relations Board (including 1938 memorandum on jurisdiction (1935-38) (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - National Maritime Union (subcommittee on finances) 1938 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - National Mediation Board (William Leiserson) 1939 (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - National Recovery Administration (Labor Studies Section) 1935 (Box 142, Folder 21)
      - National Refugee Service (1939) (Box 142, Folder 22)
      - National Surety Company (1937) (Box 142, Folder 23)
      - National Youth Administration (1936) (Box 142, Folder 24)
      - Naturalization Aid League (1935) (Box 142, Folder 25)
      - Neckwear Workers (United) 1935-40 (Box 142, Folder 26)
      - Nederlands Verband Van Vakvereniginger (1937) (Box 142, Folder 27)
      - Needlecraft Educational Commission (Advisory Board for Central High School of Needle Trades) 1946 (Box 142, Folder 28)
      - Needletrades Association of Maryland (1935) (Box 142, Folder 29)
      - Negro Labor Committee (correspondence with Winifred Gittens and Samuel Shore) 1936 (Box 142, Folder 30)
      - Neue Volkszetung (N.Y.C.) 1936-39 (Box 142, Folder 31)
      - New England Tailors Joint Board (1940) (Box 142, Folder 32)
      - New Leader (1935-36) (Box 142, Folder 33)
      - New York City (correspondence with administrators of various NYC departments including the mayor's office) 1936-39 (Box 142, Folder 34)
      - New York City Board of Higher Education (1936-39) (Box 142, Folder 35)
      - New York State. Federation of Labor (1935) (Box 142, Folder 36)
      - New York Teachers Guild (Harry Linville) 1936 (Box 142, Folder 37)
      - Newspaper Guild (American) 1935-38 (Box 142, Folder 38)
      - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League (1937) (Box 142, Folder 39)
      - North Carolina Federation of Labor (1936-37) (Box 142, Folder 40)
      - Novack, George (American Committee for the Defense of Leon Trotsky) (Box 142, Folder 41)
      - N (general) (Box 142, Folder 42)
      - Office and Professional Workers (United) request for ACWA constitution (1938) (Box 142, Folder 43)
      - Oil Workers (International Union) 1938 (Box 142, Folder 44)
      - Orr, Samuel (attorney, NYC) 1937 (Box 142, Folder 45)
      - O (general) (Box 142, Folder 46)
      - Padway, Joseph (attorney, NYC) 1935-36 (Box 142, Folder 47)
      - Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers (International Union) 1938 (Box 142, Folder 48)
      - Palestine Appeal (United) 1937-39 (Box 142, Folder 49)
      - Paper Makers (International Brotherhood) 1939 (Box 142, Folder 50)
      - Pennsylvania Federation of Labor (1936) (Box 142, Folder 51)
      - Pennsylvania Industrial Union Council (1938) (Box 142, Folder 52)
      - People's Committee for a Farmer Labor Party (1936) (Box 142, Folder 53)
      - People's Lobby (Benjamin Marsh) 1936-38 (Box 142, Folder 54)
      - Perkins, Francis (Secretary of Labor) Schlossberg to (1938) (Box 142, Folder 55)
      - Pharmacists Union of Greater N.Y. (1936) (Box 142, Folder 56)
      - Pioneer Women's Organization (1936) (Box 142, Folder 57)
      - Pioneer Youth (1935-38) (Box 142, Folder 58)
      - Piore, E.R. (1938-39) (Box 142, Folder 59)
      - Plettl, Martin (Brookwood Labor College and Vineland Shore Labor College) organizer, ACWA, Florida 1936-39 (Box 143, Folder l)
      - Pocketbook Workers Union (United Leather Workers 1936-38 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Popolo (IL) 1939 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Potofsky, Jacob (1936) (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Printing Pressmen's Association of N.Y. (George Berry) 1936 (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Pulp, Sulfite and Paper Mill Workers (International Brotherhood of) 1936 (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - P (general) (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Quarry Workers International Union (1936-38) (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Quebec Federation of Labor (1938) (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Queens College (Joseph Schlossberg as member of Board of Higher Education (1936-39) (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Rand School of Social Science (correspondence with William Bohn and Algernon Lee (1936-38) (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - Randolph, A. Philip (Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters) 1937-39 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - Rassweiler, G.F. (Beloit College, Wisconsin) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Red Caps (International Brotherhood of) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Referendum Vote (1938) (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Relief Association (International) (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Retail Clerks Protective Association of America (1935) (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Reuther, Walter (UAW) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 18)
      - Rickert, T.A. (United Garment Workers) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - Robinson, Frederick (President, City College) 1937 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin (1938) (Box 143, Folder 21)
      - Rose, Alex (State Secretary, American Labor Party) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Rosenman, Samuel (1936) (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - Rubber Workers (United) re 1936 sit down strike (Box 143, Folder 24)
      - R (general) (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - Sacramento Appeal Committee (San Francisco General Strike - 18 organizers jailed) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 26)
      - Salerno, Joseph (Textile Workers Organizing Committee) (Box 143, Folder 27)
      - Salert, Irving (NYC Board of Education) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 28)
      - Savannah, Georgia Trades and Labor Assembly (1936) (Box 143, Folder 29)
      - Schaffner, Louis (Meyer London memorial committee) 1936 (Box 143, Folder 30)
      - Schlossberg Trade Union Branch of the Journeymen Tailors Union of North America (1938) (Box 143, Folder 31)
      - Schneider, Morris (job request) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      - Schwartz, Julius and Sons (1940) (Box 143, Folder 33)
      - Seamen's International Union (strike strategy committee) 1936 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      - Seidel, Herman (1936-38) re Palestine (Box 143, Folder 34a)
      - Senior, Clarence (Socialist Party of America) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 35)
      - Sexton, Brendan (Workers Defense League) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 36)
      - Sheboygan (Wisconsin) Central Labor Council (1935) (Box 143, Folder 37)
      - Silva, Jose (Universidad National de Mexico) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 38)
      - Sobel, Norman (NYC Committee for Public Adult Education) 1937-38 (Box 143, Folder 39)
      - Social Democratic Federation (1938) (Box 143, Folder 40)
      - Social Research (Institute for) 1936 (Box 143, Folder 41)
      - Social Security Board (1936-38) (Box 143, Folder 42)
      - Socialist Call (1938) (Box 143, Folder 43)
      - Socialist Party of America (includes correspondence with members of the Executive committee, Algernon Lee and Alice Dodge, Maynard Kreuger) 1936-39 (Box 143, Folder 44)
      - Society of Friends of Yiddish Scientific Institute (1939) (Box 143, Folder 45)
      - Solidarity Fund for Spanish Democracy (1936) (Box 143, Folder 46)
      - South Dakota Federation of Labor (Box 143, Folder 47)
      - Southern Summer School for Workers (Pearl Willen) 1938 (Box 143, Folder 48)
      - Southern Tenant Farmers Union (1938-40) (Box 143, Folder 49)
      - Soviet Russia Today (1936) (Box 143, Folder 50)
      - Spitzer, Morris (Local 278, Los Angeles) 1935 (Box 143, Folder 51)
      - Springfield (Ohio) Trades & Labor Assembly (1936) (Box 143, Folder 52)